35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Schooner Bowdoin accompany this slide presentation, undated; 13 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: People on deck of boat looking at papers], 2
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Side of boat], 3
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Iceberg], 4
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man on boat, mountains ahead], 5
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat passing by mountains], 6
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man sitting on mast of ship], 7
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: People sitting on deck of boat], 8
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Side of boat], 9
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man in a yellow raincoat standing on boat], 10
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man wearing headphones, working on boat], 11
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat passinig by snowy mountains], 12
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Sailboat on water], 13
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man on boat], 14
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: People on deck of boat, mountains ahead], 15
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man on boat, sun setting], 16
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Sun setting on the horizon of ocean], 17
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat being lifted by a crane], 18
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Crane lifting a boat, "Goudy and Stevens"], 19
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Harbor], 20
  - Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Schooner Bowdoin accompany this slide presentation, undated; 14 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: People near a river], 1
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on river], 2
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: People on deck of boat], 3
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on land, a warehouse], 4
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on water,; Captioned "National Trust for Historic Preservation Challenge Grant $95,000"], 5
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on water; Captioned "Total Necessary $385,000"], 6
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on water; Captioned "$190,000 must be raised and spent by May, 1981"], 7
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Captain at wheel of boat], 8
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man on boat], 9
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Polar bear swimming], 10
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: "Bowdoin" boat, people on boat], 11
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: People watching boat arrive], 12
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on land, a warehouse], 13
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on water, Captioned "Tax Deductible Gifts"], 14
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Person at wheel of boat], 15
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: People looking at buckets on the boat], 16
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: People on deck of a boat], 17
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Person holding a fish], 18
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Person reaching up to mast of boat], 19
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man on boat], 20
  - Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Schooner Bowdoin accompany this slide presentation, undated; 15 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Two people holding onto sleds], 1
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Men walking through snow and ice], 2
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man standing by sleds and supplies], 3
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Men pulling up sled before it hits the water], 4
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat stuck in ice], 5
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on icy water], 6
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man on boat], 7
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Man on boat looking at iceberg], 8
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Sailboat], 9
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: People on land, boat docked], 10
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Person at the wheel of boat], 11
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Lowell Thomas and another man talking into CBS microphones], 12
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Mast of boat], 13
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Wave crashing at side of boat], 14
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Sun setting on horizon of ocean], 15
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on water], 16
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: People standing by boat on land], 17
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Boat on water, Captioned "Schooner Bowdoin Restoration Campaign. RFD #1 Box 726 Rockland, ME 04841"], 18
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Sun setting on horizon of ocean], 19
    - [Carousel number 26 [Schooner Bowdoin]: Rippling water, Captioned "Produced and Directed by John D. Rhodes Associates. Brunswick, Maine"], 20
  - Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University accompany this slide presentation, 1975; 16 (Box 1588)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University accompany this slide presentation [: Collage of photos, Captioned "1963 Construction. Roberts Details 4-year University Planes"], 1
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Construction vehicles], 2
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Two men riding a construction vehicle], 3
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Collage of photos, Captioned "1965 Classes Begin" (Oral Roberts University)], 4
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Collage of photos, Captioned "1967 Dedication. Graham Gives ORU Challenge In Dedication, Graham and ORU Draw Multitudes, Graham Calls for Putting Christ Back in Colleges at ORU Rites"], 5
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Two men speaking at Oral Roberts University podium], 6
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Pendant "Oral Roberts Univeristy. Mind, Spirit, Body. 1963. Tulsam Oklahoma"], 7
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Colloage of articles, Captioned "1971 Accreditation" (Oral Roberts University)], 8
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Collage of articles and photos of basketball games, Captioned "1972 ORU Titans, ORU Gets Bid to Play in NIT"], 9
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Collage of photos and articles, Captioned "1974 World Action Singers" (Oral Roberts University)], 10
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Woman raising her hands and smiling], 11
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Collage of articles from the Tulsa Tribune. "ORU Will Open Med School in 1978"], 12
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Crowd of people], 13
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Buildings on ORU campus], 14
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man speaking to crowd of people], 15
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man posing at campus of ORU], 16
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: ORU campus (?)], 17
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Four people posing for a picture in front of Prayer Tower], 18
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Close-up of man smiling], 19
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Close-up of woman smiling], 20
  - Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University accompany this slide presentation, 1975; 17 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Close-up of a woman smiling], 1
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Close-up of a man smiling], 2
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man and woman sitting down and reading], 3
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: ORU campus], 4
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Crowd of people], 5
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Flags of different nations lining the road], 6
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Woman studying in a library], 7
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: A band, people playing trumpets, french horns, and trombones], 8
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Students sitting in a class], 9
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Woman looking through a microscope], 10
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Professor teaching at blackboard], 11
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Pamphlets titled ''The Spirit-filled Word"and "Training Managers for A.D. 2000"], 12
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: A building on ORU campus], 13
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Sign that reads "Ralph L. Reece" located in front of building], 14
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man and woman studying in a library], 15
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man looking through bookshelf at library], 16
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Portrait of a man], 17
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Two men with headphones watching a man on television], 18
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Woman sitting in a chair at library], 19
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People working in a media room], 20
  - Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University accompany this slide presentation, 1975; 18 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man and woman looking at papers], 1
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man teaching a class], 2
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man listening to records], 3
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People working behind cameras], 4
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man looking through microscope], 5
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man and woman working in lab], 6
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man sitting behind a desk], 7
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Two men sitting on a couch, talking], 8
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Professor talking to a student], 9
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man talking to a group of people], 10
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Woman with a microphone talking to a man], 11
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Woman working on a project], 12
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People acting on stage], 13
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Domed building], 14
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Sidewalk running by building], 15
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man playing the trombone], 16
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: School choir performing], 17
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: A building], 18
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People performing gymnastics], 19
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People performing gymnastics], 20
  - Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University accompany this slide presentation, 1975; 19 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Boys playing basketball], 1
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Three people presenting a plaque that reads "Kenneth H. Cooper Aerobics Center"], 2
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People walking on a sidewalk], 3
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Women on exercise bikes], 4
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Woman running on sidewalk], 5
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Men running around an indoor track], 6
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People doing gymnastics], 7
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People playing badmitton], 8
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Indoor swimming pool], 9
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man playing tennis], 10
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Boys sitting in dugout], 11
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Woman on treadmill], 12
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man on bike, breathing into a machine], 13
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Men playng basketball], 14
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man hittign baseball], 15
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man playing golf], 16
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Men huddled around coach], 17
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Men playing basketball], 18
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man speaking into microphone on basketball court], 19
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Men playing basketball], 20
  - Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University] Note: An audio cassette recording and a transcript titled Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University accompany this slide presentation, 1975; 20 (Box 1588)
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Buildings on campus], 1
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man walking on sidewalk], 2
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man walking on sidewalk], 3
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Buildings and a parking lot], 4
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Fountains and a building], 5
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: People eating ina cafeteria], 6
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man giving a lecture in a lecture hall], 7
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Four women havign drinks at a table], 8
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Man speaking at podium], 9
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Woman at podium speaking], 10
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Band playing on stage], 11
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Theatre], 12
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Group of people together, smiling], 13
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: A cheerleader], 14
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Cheering crowd], 15
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: A cheerleader], 16
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Basketball game], 17
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Two men with TVS microphones talking with another man], 18
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Scoreboard that reads "We Won!"], 19
    - [Carousel number 27 [Prayer Tower Presentation, Oral Roberts University]: Building], 20
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1